{
    "subject": "resource/South_China_AA",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "resource/Andy_Russell_(English_footballer)",
    "human_readable": "The name of South China AA is Andy Russell (English footballer).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.926124095916748,
            "question": "Does Andy Russell play for South China AA?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8810615539550781,
            "question": "What is the name of South China AA?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8763089776039124,
            "question": "Who is known as South China AA?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8072846531867981,
            "question": "Is Andy Russell a famous footballer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.802268385887146,
            "question": "Is there a famous athlete named Andy Russell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7979384660720825,
            "question": "What is the full name of Andy Russell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7901645302772522,
            "question": "Who is Andy Russell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7403634786605835,
            "question": "What nationality is Andy Russell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6929064989089966,
            "question": "Where does Andy Russell play football?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4760279953479767,
            "question": "What sport does Andy Russell play?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of South China AA is Andy Russell (English footballer).",
            "html": "dbpedia_4891_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where does Andy Russell play football?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4891_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is Andy Russell?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4891_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Andy Russell?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4891_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4891_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4891_132.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4891_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4891_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4891_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4891_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4891_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4891_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4891_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4891_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents contain information about the South China Athletic Association and its teams, as well as a player named Andy Russell. However, there is no mention of the name \"Andy Russell\" being associated with the team's official name or any indication that his English name is \"South China AA.\" Therefore, the statement \"The name of South China AA is Andy Russell (English footballer)\" is not supported by the given documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}